[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBD", "NNP", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 24, "question": "Did the president call?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "the", "president", "call", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 25, "answer": "NIDENTIFIED FEMALE: No.", "answer_tokens": ["NIDENTIFIED", "FEMALE", ":", "No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "Why did you wait so long to tell them?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "wait", "so", "long", "to", "tell", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "I was told not to communicate with them.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "told", "not", "to", "communicate", "with", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "And also to his public apology?", "question_tokens": ["And", "also", "to", "his", "public", "apology", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "Well, the family was prepared for George Zimmerman getting a bail.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "family", "was", "prepared", "for", "George", "Zimmerman", "getting", "a", "bail", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "I mean, can you really blame him for wanting to do what everyone's been screaming at him to do?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "can", "you", "really", "blame", "him", "for", "wanting", "to", "do", "what", "everyone", "'s", "been", "screaming", "at", "him", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "WP", "NN", "POS", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "Well, the apology is for the family.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "apology", "is", "for", "the", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "Are they prepared for that eventuality?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "prepared", "for", "that", "eventuality", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "Well, this family has said all along that they have full faith in the justice system.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "this", "family", "has", "said", "all", "along", "that", "they", "have", "full", "faith", "in", "the", "justice", "system", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "Would you have expected that knowing Florida law as you do?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "have", "expected", "that", "knowing", "Florida", "law", "as", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Well, it was a discretionary call by the judge.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "a", "discretionary", "call", "by", "the", "judge", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Florida"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Miami"]}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "Do you agree with what he just said?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "agree", "with", "what", "he", "just", "said", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "Piers, I have been in a legal community in Miami for well over 20 years.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "I", "have", "been", "in", "a", "legal", "community", "in", "Miami", "for", "well", "over", "20", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "JJS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "I mean, what did you make of what they were saying?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "what", "did", "you", "make", "of", "what", "they", "were", "saying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Well, I don't really agree with at least the last commentator.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "really", "agree", "with", "at", "least", "the", "last", "commentator", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "Would you be confident if you were defending George Zimmerman now from everything you've seen, read, and heard?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "be", "confident", "if", "you", "were", "defending", "George", "Zimmerman", "now", "from", "everything", "you", "'ve", "seen", ",", "read", ",", "and", "heard", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "RB", ",", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "Well, Piers, I was really sort of shocked watching this hearing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "was", "really", "sort", "of", "shocked", "watching", "this", "hearing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "What's your gut tell you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "gut", "tell", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Well, it may be they're holding it back.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "may", "be", "they", "'re", "holding", "it", "back", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "How do you expect a judge to do a decent job in making a ruling when you don't give him any evidence?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "expect", "a", "judge", "to", "do", "a", "decent", "job", "in", "making", "a", "ruling", "when", "you", "do", "n't", "give", "him", "any", "evidence", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "What do you feel about it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "Well, I'm -- you know, I -- I can't -- I feel that the pain, you know, that the family is going through.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "--", "you", "know", ",", "I", "--", "I", "ca", "n't", "--", "I", "feel", "that", "the", "pain", ",", "you", "know", ",", "that", "the", "family", "is", "going", "through", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", ":", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "Do you think that George Zimmerman was a racist who targeted Trayvon because he was black?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "George", "Zimmerman", "was", "a", "racist", "who", "targeted", "Trayvon", "because", "he", "was", "black", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "Well, I -- what I think is the laws are - the rules are old.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "--", "what", "I", "think", "is", "the", "laws", "are", "-", "the", "rules", "are", "old", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "What do you think of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Well, you know, it's probably an old stigma also because you got to look at the -- you know, the way our country was built.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "probably", "an", "old", "stigma", "also", "because", "you", "got", "to", "look", "at", "the", "--", "you", "know", ",", "the", "way", "our", "country", "was", "built", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "When you wrote the book, what are your feelings when you finished it towards the officers who did what they did to you that day 21 years ago?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "wrote", "the", "book", ",", "what", "are", "your", "feelings", "when", "you", "finished", "it", "towards", "the", "officers", "who", "did", "what", "they", "did", "to", "you", "that", "day", "21", "years", "ago", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "First of all, thank goodness that I stayed alive.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "thank", "goodness", "that", "I", "stayed", "alive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "Have you forgiven, in your mind, the policemen that did what they did?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "forgiven", ",", "in", "your", "mind", ",", "the", "policemen", "that", "did", "what", "they", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Going forward?", "question_tokens": ["Going", "forward", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "How do you feel now about the police?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "now", "about", "the", "police", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "I have much respect for them, much respect.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "much", "respect", "for", "them", ",", "much", "respect", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "I love the way you were laughing so uncomfortably at yourself dancing there.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "the", "way", "you", "were", "laughing", "so", "uncomfortably", "at", "yourself", "dancing", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "Well, I mean, could you imagine if you were dancing like that?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "could", "you", "imagine", "if", "you", "were", "dancing", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Oh, it is?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "it", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "Pretty much, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Pretty", "much", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "Do you still look on scenes like that with great affection or does it become this terrible curse you wish you'd ever been involved with?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "look", "on", "scenes", "like", "that", "with", "great", "affection", "or", "does", "it", "become", "this", "terrible", "curse", "you", "wish", "you", "'d", "ever", "been", "involved", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "Hardly.", "answer_tokens": ["Hardly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "\"Seinfeld\"?", "question_tokens": ["``", "Seinfeld", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "WRB", "JJ", ":", "RB", "TO", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "At moment when you first start making (INAUDIBLE), at what moment do you start thinking -- actually this could be huge?", "question_tokens": ["At", "moment", "when", "you", "first", "start", "making", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", ",", "at", "what", "moment", "do", "you", "start", "thinking", "--", "actually", "this", "could", "be", "huge", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", ":", "RB", "DT", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "I think I never really caught up to how big -- honestly to how big it was until right before we ended.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "never", "really", "caught", "up", "to", "how", "big", "--", "honestly", "to", "how", "big", "it", "was", "until", "right", "before", "we", "ended", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "I swear to you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "swear", "to", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "Didn't like 100 million people watch that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "n't", "like", "100", "million", "people", "watch", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "I don't remember.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "remember", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "It was like a Super Bowl, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "like", "a", "Super", "Bowl", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "Do we have a fact checker here?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "we", "have", "a", "fact", "checker", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "If I'm exaggerating, go with me.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "I", "'m", "exaggerating", ",", "go", "with", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "Do you have like little \"Seinfeld\" reunions in some dingy little bar in Manhattan?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "like", "little", "``", "Seinfeld", "''", "reunions", "in", "some", "dingy", "little", "bar", "in", "Manhattan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "``", "NNP", "''", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "We get together on a daily basis.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "get", "together", "on", "a", "daily", "basis", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Manhattan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "Do the ships just pass out of the port and that's it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "the", "ships", "just", "pass", "out", "of", "the", "port", "and", "that", "'s", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "We do see each other on occasion.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "do", "see", "each", "other", "on", "occasion", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "What is it about that show, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "about", "that", "show", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Well, I think it's a couple things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "couple", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "Don't you have a bleeper here?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "you", "have", "a", "bleeper", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "Yes, we're going to have to now.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "have", "to", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "Did you have more or less sympathy for her by the end of your process, just on what it takes to be a vice president?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "more", "or", "less", "sympathy", "for", "her", "by", "the", "end", "of", "your", "process", ",", "just", "on", "what", "it", "takes", "to", "be", "a", "vice", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "I have more sympathy for all women in government.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "more", "sympathy", "for", "all", "women", "in", "government", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palins"]}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RBR", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "More Sarah Palins?", "question_tokens": ["More", "Sarah", "Palins", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "No, not more Sarah Palins in my opinion.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "more", "Sarah", "Palins", "in", "my", "opinion", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palins"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", ":", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 543, "question": "No, I mean just generally for women in America right now?", "question_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "mean", "just", "generally", "for", "women", "in", "America", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "Well, it's interesting because all of these issues are -- trans-vaginal probes and --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "interesting", "because", "all", "of", "these", "issues", "are", "--", "trans-vaginal", "probes", "and", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "Are you expecting some sharp flip-flopping?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "expecting", "some", "sharp", "flip-flopping", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "I know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "What do you make of your country right now generally?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "your", "country", "right", "now", "generally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "I love it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "What is the solution for America?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "solution", "for", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "I have no idea.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "no", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "How are we going to get there?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "we", "going", "to", "get", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "For my children, I want my children to be active.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "my", "children", ",", "I", "want", "my", "children", "to", "be", "active", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "What else?", "question_tokens": ["What", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "That's good.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "You do?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "Yes, it's why you should be running for office.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "'s", "why", "you", "should", "be", "running", "for", "office", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "What office do you think I should run for?", "question_tokens": ["What", "office", "do", "you", "think", "I", "should", "run", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "I would go on the anti-transvaginal probe brigade.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "go", "on", "the", "anti-transvaginal", "probe", "brigade", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "What part of that character did he fall in love with?", "question_tokens": ["What", "part", "of", "that", "character", "did", "he", "fall", "in", "love", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "I'm not sure any part of it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "sure", "any", "part", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "Yeah, you think?", "question_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "Yes, definitely.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "definitely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "How have the pair of you, who are in the same profession, managed to stay happily married for 25 years?", "question_tokens": ["How", "have", "the", "pair", "of", "you", ",", "who", "are", "in", "the", "same", "profession", ",", "managed", "to", "stay", "happily", "married", "for", "25", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "Well, let's see, first of all, we're separating.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "'s", "see", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "we", "'re", "separating", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 675, "question": "How did you know he was the right guy?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "know", "he", "was", "the", "right", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 676, "answer": "Here's the deal.", "answer_tokens": ["Here", "'s", "the", "deal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 689, "question": "Do you feel lucky?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "lucky", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 690, "answer": "I do feel lucky.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "feel", "lucky", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 697, "question": "Do you make each other laugh?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "make", "each", "other", "laugh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 698, "answer": "Oh, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "``", "NNP", "''", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "Because there's an \"SNL\" battle every day?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "there", "'s", "an", "``", "SNL", "''", "battle", "every", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "``", "NNP", "''", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "No, it's not an \"SNL\" battle.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "an", "``", "SNL", "''", "battle", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 710, "question": "Are you seriously about to split up?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "seriously", "about", "to", "split", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 711, "answer": "No, I'm kidding.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "kidding", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120420pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 725, "question": "What could go wrong?", "question_tokens": ["What", "could", "go", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 726, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]